const STORE = [
	{
		question: 'What is the first year the Devils qualified for the Stanley Cup Playoffs?',
		answerChoices: [
			'2000',
			'1982',
			'1988',
			'1995'
			],
		correctAnswer: '1988',
		answerStatement: `The first year the Devils qualified for the Stanley Cup Playoffs was in ${this.correctAnswer}!`,
		funFact: 'The Devils clinched a playoff spot in the last game of the 1988 regular season, with a win against the Blackhawks.'
	},
	{
		question: 'Who scored the Stanley Cup winning goal for the Devils in 1995?',
		answerChoices: [
			'Scott Stevens',
			'Claude Lemieux',
			'Neal Broten',
			'Stephan Richer'
			],
		correctAnswer: 'Neal Broten',
		answerStatement: `${this.correctAnswer} scored the Stanley Cup winning goal for the Devils in 1995!`,
		funFact: 'Neal Broten became one of the few American-born players to score a Cup winning goal.'
	},
	{
		question: 'In which of the following seasons, did Martin Brodeur win the Calder Trophy?',
		answerChoices: [
			'1995-1996',
			'1999-2000',
			'1994-1995',
			'1993-1994'
			],
		correctAnswer: '1993-1994',
		answerStatement: `Martin Brodeur won the Calder Trophy in ${this.correctAnswer}!`,
		funFact: 'Martin Brodeur and Scott Gomez are the only players in New Jersey Devils history to ever win the Calder Trophy.'
	},
	{
		question: 'Who was the coach of the Devils\' 2000 Stanley Cup winning team?',
		answerChoices: [
			'Jacques Lemaire',
			'Pat Burns',
			'Lou Lamoriello',
			'Larry Robinson'
			],
		correctAnswer: 'Larry Robinson',
		answerStatement: `${this.correctAnswer} was the coach of the Devils' Stanley Cup winning team!`,
		funFact: 'Larry Robinson, Hall of Fame defenseman, was nicknamed "Big Bird", during his playing days in Montreal.'
	},
	{
		question: 'In how many games did the Devils win the 1995 Stanley Cup Final?',
		answerChoices: [
			'5',
			'4',
			'6',
			'7'
			],
		correctAnswer: '4',
		answerStatement: `The Devils swept the 1995 Stanley Cup Finals in ${this.correctAnswer} games!`,
		funFact: 'In the 1995 season, the Devils captured their first Stanley Cup in a 4 game sweep, of the heavily favored Detroit Red Wings.'
	},
	{
		question: 'At the start of the Devils franchise, where did they play and what was their team name?',
		answerChoices: [
			'Kansas City Scouts',
			'Colorado Rockies',
			'New Jersey Devils',
			'Brooklyn Americans'
			],
		correctAnswer: 'Kansas City Scouts',
		answerStatement: `In 1974, the Devils\' franchise started out as the ${this.correctAnswer}!`,
		funFact: 'Two years after the start of the franchise, the Scouts moved to Denver and became the Colorado Rockies.'
	},
	{
		question: 'In the 1998 NHL Entry Draft, what round did the Devils select Scott Gomez?',
		answerChoices: [
			'3rd',
			'6th',
			'1st',
			'4th'
			],
		correctAnswer: '1st',
		answerStatement: `The Devils selected Scott Gomez with their ${this.correctAnswer} round pick in the 1998 Entry Draft!`,
		funFact: 'Scott justified the Devilsâ€™ decision by scoring 108 points in 58 games for the Tri-City Americans of the WHL.'
	},
	{
		question: 'Who was the Captain of the New Jersey Devils in 2003?',
		answerChoices: [
			'Patrik Elias',
			'Jamie Langenbrunner',
			'Scott Niedermayer',
			'Scott Stevens'
			],
		correctAnswer: 'Scott Stevens',
		answerStatement: `The Captain of the New Jersey Devils in 2003 was ${this.correctAnswer}!`,
		funFact: 'Scott Stevens captained the New Jersey Devils from 1992 to 2004, for a total of 12 straight seasons.'
	},
	{
		question: 'The New Jersey Devils held a 20 game unbeaten streak against which rivals?',
		answerChoices: [
			'New York Rangers',
			'Philadelphia Flyers',
			'New York Islanders',
			'Carolina Hurricanes'
			],
		correctAnswer: 'New York Rangers',
		answerStatement: `The Devils held a 20 game unbeaten streak against the ${this.correctAnswer}!`,
		funFact: 'The Devils scored 72 goals to the Rangers 38, and managed 14 wins, six ties, and one shutout over this span.'
	},
	{
		question: 'What was the last year the color green was a part of the Devils wardrobe?',
		answerChoices: [
			'1995',
			'1988',
			'1992',
			'2000'
			],
		correctAnswer: '1992',
		answerStatement: `The Devils wore the color green as a part of their wardrobe for the last time in ${this.correctAnswer}!`,
		funFact: 'The green on the jerseys was removed and replaced with black, and less stripes appeared on the sweater as well.'
	}
];